Guide to the Jack and Rebecca Matlock Papers, 1930s-2017 RL.11082
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1980-2016; 740 items
  - Miscellaneous audiovisual
    - Shilov, undated (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0109)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0515, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0109.mp4)
    - Cold War-Berlin Wall, undated (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0111)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0517, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0111.mp4)
    - Yeltsin, Pacem Distibution International, The National Bureau of Asian Research, undated (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0114)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0520, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0114.mp4)
    - Direct Connection, undated (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0117)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0523, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0117.mp4)
    - Adam Smith on Russia (JFM), undated (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0118)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0524, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0118.mp4)
    - Direct Connection US-USSR and World Comm. Init., undated (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0119)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0525, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0119.mp4)
    - untitled, undated (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0120)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0526, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0120.mp4)
    - untitled, undated (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0133)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0539, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0133.mp4)
    - untitled, undated (Box AV04, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0135)
    - Documentary Film "Belated Kadish", Georgia TV Film Company, undated (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0136)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0541, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0136.mp4)
    - untitled, undated (Box AV05, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0136)
    - untitled, undated (Box AV06, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0173)
      - Digital video file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0578, Video-file RL11082-VHS-0173.mp4)
    - untitled, undated (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0200)
    - House-warming American inspection in Votkinsk, undated (Box AV19, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0205)
    - Ambassador Matlock - Riga - Tape 2 - Glen Pearly Productions, undated (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0235)
    - Ambassador Matlock - Riga - Tape 1 - Glen Pearly Productions, undated (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0242)
    - untitled, undated (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0250)
    - Party conference news, Yakovlev press conference, undated (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0258)
    - шатров - "ъольшевцкц"; Владимир Ленин - страницы жизни (I), undated (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0262)
    - untitled, undated (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0267)
    - больше света, undated (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0283)
    - одинокий ожотник, undated (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0287)
    - Khas; Volsky, undated (Box AV22, Audio-cassette RL11082-MCS-0038)
    - Afanasiev, undated (Box AV22, Audio-cassette RL11082-MCS-0043)
    - untitled, undated (Box AV22, Audio-cassette RL11082-MCS-0049)
    - [Title TBD], undated (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0277)
    - [Title TBD], undated (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0278)
    - untitled, undated (Box AV20, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0250)
    - Party conference news, Yakovlev press conference, undated (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0258)
    - шатров - "ъольшевцкц"; Владимир Ленин - страницы жизни (I), undated (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0262)
    - untitled, undated (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0267)
    - больше света, undated (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0283)
    - одинокий ожотник, undated (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0287)
    - Khas; Volsky, undated (Box AV22, Audio-cassette RL11082-MCS-0038)
      - Digital audio file (Digital-materials RL11082-SET-0001, Object RL11082-MCS-0038.mp3)
    - Afanasiev, undated (Box AV22, Audio-cassette RL11082-MCS-0043)
    - untitled, undated (Box AV22, Audio-cassette RL11082-MCS-0049)
    - [Title TBD], undated (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0277)
    - [Title TBD], undated (Box AV21, Video-cassette RL11082-VHS-0278)